{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4105","name":"Onassis Coney Island","address":"1501 Michigan","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Marjan Gjolaj","licenseNumber":"070392","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Plan Review","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.06739,42.33111","geojson":{"id":"4105","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.067394843,42.3311054480001]},"properties":{"name":"Onassis Coney Island","owner":"Marjan Gjolaj","address":"1501 Michigan","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"070392","establishmentid":"4105","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Plan Review","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/26/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"500","name":"McShane's","address":"1460 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4938","name":"UFO Factory","address":"2110 Trumbull St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","address":"1950 Trumbull Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4781","name":"Bucharest Grill","address":"1623 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4648","name":"Ottava Via","address":"1400 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"545","name":"Nemos","address":"1378 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622591","name":"The Farmer's Hand LLC /DBA Folk","address":"1701 Trumbull Ste B","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51622639","name":"Meta Physica Wellness Center","address":"1701 Trumbull Ste 3","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51622463","name":"Corktown Tavern Inc.","address":"1716 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"5416","name":"Lady of the House, LLC","address":"1426 Bagley Ave","zipcode":"48216"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44109","inspectionDate":"2018-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s) knives","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Between the Equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Knives","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the floor Food products","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"41969","inspectionDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"On the floor Frozen Food(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease extraction filters","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Ice machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40061","inspectionDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37924","inspectionDate":"2017-01-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ÂºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ÂºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ÂºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-04-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4105"}}